I can't believe you're here right now.
How could you have died?
How?
That can't be real.
We've had a long way to go with you,
brother.
I wish...
I wish I hadn't hung out this long after
Alaca left the club.
You wouldn't have thought of this
party, either.
You'd be looking at your job for strength.
And none of that would happen.
Forgive me, brother.
I don't dare look at your face.
Please, forgive me.
I'm sorry, Professor.
We have to take it now.
Bye, brother.
Of course, we'll see you again.
Bye.
Yep.
Did you find his place?
I know the hospital.
Okay, thanks.
I'm so sorry bro, too.
The call never deserved it.
Why did this happen, brother?
I don't know, Gokhan.
Life...
... gives us the answers to some
questions later.
We will live and learn.
Let's see what else life can teach us.
God, I don't understand.
I'm gonna freak out eventually.
Come on.
Come on, son.
I'm already holding myself hard.
I don't know, brother.
I really don't know anything anymore.
What should I do, huh?
Tell me what to do?
Our best days have passed with The Call.
If it wasn't for him...
I was a jerk in America.
What we ate and what we drank would
not go apart.
His family...
He would see me as his son.
The latest...
... When I got on the phone with Aunt
Gülseren...
...” My son is entrusted to you.”
What am I gonna tell him now, huh?
Yes Tolga Abi...
How do I tell him your brother's dead huh?
Abi!
Still no answer?
No, I can't reach.
Dad, did you learn anything?
I found out which hospital he was in.
I'm going there now.
All right.
Which hospital? I'll come, too.
No. Unique.
We can't go there like the family goes to
visit the community.
It's not our hospital.
I'm gonna go.
I'll find out everything.
You will be waiting to hear from me.
Dad, please.
- I want to be with Kenan. - Don't insist.
I know what I'm saying.
Daughter, that's what your father said,
which he knew.
All right. All right, Dad.
My daughter.
Don't cry anymore.
You've ruined yourself.
Look, it's too bad for you.
Shame on me?
Shame on the original call.
Because of me, the young man left.
Because of you?
Oh, what kind of word is that?
If I hadn't come into their lives, they
would be alive now.
He was in the gym now, maybe he was
at work.
Maybe they went to the movies with
Jasmine.
Maybe he was talking to his mother.
Maybe...
Look, girl.
It will not be lived with beggars,
nor with monks.
It means that the foreword is like that.
Turan, I wish he'd killed me.
If he'd killed me, if he hadn't done
anything to him.
Girl, what a way you talk!
Don't do that.
Look, you have a beautiful girl.
Think about it for a bit.
Come on, don't do that.
You have to stand strong.
Look, girl...
Look, he's sleeping inside now.
Coming to her in a moment...
If he sees you crying in a fountain with
two eyes like that...
Will it ever be?
Look, you're gonna stay strong...
... so he can hold on to you.
First of all, you are a mother.
Don't forget that, please.
That bastard will serve his sentence.
Don't worry about it.
The wick will come through the wick nose.
My daughter, don't cry anymore.
Don't cry.
Hello. Pinarcissus, are you available?
Yes, I'm listening, dear.
We don't have any information.
But my father found out about the
hospital that the Call stayed.
He's even going there now.
Which hospital was it?
He didn't tell me either.
But my father would call if there was
any improvement.
What am I saying, do you have a call
to find out where they are?
All right.
Okay, honey, I'll try.
If I get any news, I'll call.
All right.
All right, then, we'll get in touch,
honey.
All right, then, we'll get in touch, honey
I'll see you.
I think Jasmine will sleep longer.
And you're here.
If I go and see Kenan.
It's miserable now.
So, of course, go, girl...
I didn't know, what would I do when I
woke up?
I mean, when you wake up, he wants
to see what he wants to see.
You're right. You're right.
When Jasmine awakens, I will come to
Kenan.
It would be good.
And Kenan is not alone.
He's got Gokhan with him.
You're right.
Don't stay up, sit down late.
Late, baby, late.
Ah, my Alaca.
Baki Bey.
Kenan.
I found out this morning from Yiricik.
I'm sorry, of course.
So I'm here to see if there's anything I
can do.
Thank you.
Thank you, too...
Where did the only one hear it?
He talked to Pinar.
He said it.
Of course, Biricik was also very upset.
Yeah...
Why did you bring it here?
I wish you had brought it to our hospital.
We'd take care of your friend in private.
If the ambulance was the nearest
hospital, he brought it there.
I couldn't intervene because I wasn't
there at the time.
Anyway.
These are not important.
What matters is the life of your friend.
How's he, okay?
I'm sorry.
We lost the call.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for your head.
Thank you, Baki.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Right now I just want to be alone.
I'm sorry, please.
You can tell the only one.
Please don't come.
All right.
How would you feel good.
I don't know how to do it yet, but...
I still have to meet Call's family.
So I need to get my act together in a
moment.
Because of the pain I'm going through...
I don't want anyone to come and
comfort me.
I understand you.
Don't worry at all.
Whatever you want, everything will be
like that.
Thank you again for your head.
Hello.
Where are you?
Okay, I'm coming.
Where is this idiot?
The person you are looking for cannot
be reached at this time.
No, she's still off the phone.
If I knew what was going on.
What if this idiot Turan got caught?
Then you're ruined, you're done.
Was there anything else I could help?
No. Thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
I guess I was parodying it.
Attribution.
What's the name of the boy you got
that organ from?
Call someone named Levent.
God damn it!
What happened?
Are you sure?
It's nice.
Look, this is very good news.
I think you can handle this very quickly.
All right. I trust you.
You said he was a young man, didn't you?
And the organ was not damaged at all.
Is it true?
So, does blood and tissue keep harmony?
Yes, there are a few risky situations,
but...
This is the donor we're looking for.
One minute, one minute.
Wait, I'm thinking something.
All right.
Sometimes for someone to live...
Unfortunately, someone has to lose
their life.
Do what needs to be done.
The patient's condition is already
not very good.
Having found such a suitable donor...
... can't wait.
Is there a problem, Baki?
I assure you.
Everything is as we know it.
It was done in the usual way.
There is no such thing as to arouse doubt.
Attribution can't be a problem with
the method anyway.
I designed that method step by step.
The problem is with the deceased.
In the person who died?
The dead boy turned out to be familiar.
That wasn't good.
Security cameras as usualwere
broken during the operation?
Yes, yes.
Don't worry, there will be no
problem with cameras.
So how much of this kid's liver did
you take?
Here is 70-80 percent.
Did this kid live another minute after
the operation?
It took him an hour or two to die.
There is no doubt in him either.
So it will raise any doubts, has
nothing happened?
No, Mr. Baki.
Attribution, you still review
everything one by one.
We have to think about even
the slightest possibility.
Okay, Mr. Baki.
You'll let me know.
You command.
Baki, you ordered me.
Salih. Salih.
That man gave you all the trouble?
I don't understand, Baki.
You don't understand, do you?
You didn't understand.
Let me tell you.
I used to give you a job.
You'd know it down to the smallest detail.
Now I'm giving you a job.
You can't even find out the most
important point.
Baki, if I have a problem, tell me.
I'll make it up to him right now.
Salih!
You will learn everything from the
beginning, not after it happens.
You have this coyote you're questioning...
He stabbed Kenan's friend.
Is Kenan Bey's friend?
“Is Kenan a friend of Bey?”
Do you know what it's called?
Call.
Call Levent.
Do you know what happened to the
man, Salih?
He's dead.
He's dead, he's dead!
Do you understand?
He's dead!
Do your job properly!
The guy in his hand is walking around
like a knife.
He's stabbing.
You don't know.
You used to dust off the iron when you
hit it with your hand.
Now your hand is like cotton.
Excuse me, Baki, I-
Don't talk, don't answer me.
Do your job.
Now go to that man!
Do you break your fingers or break your
legs,
Take your teeth out, whatever you do,
talk to that man!
Do you understand?
I understand, Baki.
Get out of my sight!
“Was Kenan a friend of the Lord?”
Stupid bastard!
If I don't do everything or learn
everything, the world has no idea!
I'll call you later.
I'm not available right now.
I'll get some air.
Previously...
I always thought this kind of thing
happened to other people.
My brother was stabbed first.
And then my best friend.
Life...
He forgave me my brother.
But my best friend...
He took it away from me.
So how are we going to deal with them?
We won't be able to cope.
We'll just get used to it.
The time will come...
... will close our ears.
It will make our hearts callus.
This way we will get used to it.
Kenan...
Your presence gives me strength.
Whenever I have a headache...
I think Kenan has a shoulder.
Would you feel that way too?
We're going to get through this together.
Abi!
Look at me!
Brother, what did I do again?
Boy, you walk around the neighborhood
and dust
Are you confusing me with coyotes?
Damn you!
Brother, I don't understand anything.
What do you mean, brother?
I've been sitting here all day, doing
nothing, bro.
Turan!
My son, to tear this from the sins that
you have done
Are you pretending to be crazy, huh?
This is not a court, my lion.
You make him a judge in court.
Unless, of course, I can cut it before
then.
Why are you mad at me again?
Brother, what did I do?
Didn't I tell you everything, I love your
eyes, brother?
I told you everything.
So you told me everything!
Yeah.
Boy, you stabbed a man.
Why don't you tell me?
How do I know it's important?
I mean, sometimes I stab a guy, bro.
If you're talking about this last
incident...
Abi pulled up, came out and hit me.
I had to.
I stabbed me out of necessity.
I swear I had to, brother.
I love your brother's eye.
I told you everything.
So you're stabbing a guy, huh, Turan?
You hide something from me again...
No.
I'll cut off those fingers of yours.
Come on, let's see.
Let's see who's a psychopath.
Abi.
God, I'm going crazy, help me.
Sir Pinar, sir, what is it?
I was just wondering how you were
doing, Gokhan.
You wondered how I was doing?
Let me tell you.
Because of you, because of me,
a young friend of ours died.
Because of the evil we both have done...
... the young human being will enter
the land of the Pınar.
If you have a little conscience, tell me.
How should I be?
Tell me!
Gokhan, I'm curious about you, but
I don't have it.
Don't worry, Pinar, I'm not gonna be okay.
I'm not going to be any good from now on.
I won't be any better from now on.
[What am I going to do now, what am I
going to do?]
[If this idiot is caught...
What if he talks about everything...
... then I'll be ruined.]
[I hope without being a retard
Thou hast not escaped with that
effigy, Turan.]
[No, not here so I can't wait.]
[I have to go and do something.]
Dad, welcome.
Seconds.
Can you get me a whiskey?
Dad, what happened? Is there any
news of The Call?
Dad, please say something.
I'm going to die of curiosity. How was
the call?
Thanks, Seconds.
Bon appetit, sir.
The situation is not very good.
Unique...
Unfortunately, the Call passed away.
Oh, my God!
It's terrible.
What will her parents do now?
It is not a bearable pain.
I need to call Kenan right now.
I even have to go with him.
I'll get out right now.
Wait, wait, sit down, Biricik.
Just calm down first. Look...
Kenan thinks he'll let his family know
right now.
And then he has to do a lot of other
things.
You'd better not go and stay here.
Dad, so...
He's the man I'm going to marry.
If I am not with him in this painful day,
when will I be?
Okay, I understand.
But now Kenan needs to be left alone.
Look, I wanted to stay.
He didn't accept my help either.
We also have his...
... we need to hear that thought.
Okay?
I mean, it's better if you don't leave and
stay here.
You go to him when he comes to himself.
Dad, you don't understand me at all.
You don't act like that if you understand.
I want to be with the man I love.
I want to share his pain.
Unique.
Daughter, your father is only Kenan,
even you now
He says he can't see it.
Look, he doesn't want her around, he
wants to be alone.
I understand you very well.
I'd think of it as if I were you.
But let Kenan get to his senses.
Princess, sit back.
Calm down a little.
Think about it.
I'm sure you'll make healthier decisions.
I don't want to think about anything.
Melody.
Gokhan.
I'm in a lot of pain.
In order not to cry all the time next to
the silk, I run away somewhere.
Emel's sister is also looking at her
thankfully.
I can keep up with you playing games
or something.
How am I supposed to look at you and
Canaan's face?
I can't even breathe without suffering
anymore.
Melody, please.
Please don't say anything, Gokhan.
I don't know how I'm going to live with
this torment of conscience.
It's like a knife is cutting me in half.
I can't stand it anymore.
Melody, we all suffer.
But we're gonna wrap these wounds
together.
If it wasn't for me, there wouldn't be a
wound like this.
The call was now alive.
That's why I will never forgive myself.
And not at all.
This is what happens if you cooperate
with such an idiot, Pinar.
So go ahead and get that car, get out
of here.
You can't be as smart as you can't
figure it out!
And you're getting really into the mafia
business, Pınar.
If you don't have a job, destroy this car
now.
Where is the alaca?
Jasmine just walked up to her.
I just spoke to Ezgi.
She sounded so bad.
Shall we talk about this later, brother?
Brother, please.
She's already miserable.
What's her fault if a maniac is after her?
Gokhan.
Even if he is right...
I'm not in a position to think this is
healthy right now.
Okay?
The person who suffers...
He thinks through his pain.
No matter how sad we are...
She's so sad, bro.
That coyote stabbed you, Gokhan.
Before I'm glad you're getting better
He took my best friend from me.
What do you expect me to think?
Look, brother.
I just need some time.
Just a little time.
A mountain fell on me.
Please don't expect me to get up from
gold in a day.
Hello Tolga brother.
How will the laughing aunt get through
this pain?
He will never make it through.
He won't make it through.
How much life he has left...
He will live with this pain.
What's his...
... nor Tolga's brother...
He won't laugh at any time.
They will breathe and breathe.
But he's not gonna be name-calling, is he?
Whenever they see a knife...
That knife will be stick into their hearts
There's this bastard...
... ruined everyone's lives.
Yours, mine, Aunt Gülsaran, Tolga's
brother, Jasmine.
And now he walks around waving his
hand to the armhole.
My son!
My mother!
Let my breath pass to you, Mother.
Chalk.
Get up! Son, get up!
Get up, boy!
I beg you, Mom, get up, Mom, get up!
- Get up, boy! -Mom!
Mom!
Doctor! Call a doctor!
Mom, what happens!
Help! Doctor!
Mom, get up!
Mom, get up! Mom!
Mom, get up! Get up, what happens!
Get up, Mom!
I'm so sorry.
Unfortunately, we lost the call.
My teacher.
Do you think everything was going well?
The surgery was successful.
So what happened all of a sudden now?
Believe me, I don't know either.
The values fell so quickly that we did
not understand them.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sure.
Where's Abi?
Wait for me here, I'll be right here.
Orhan Hoca.
Oh, my Master Kenan, come on.
When I saw you, I wanted to come and
talk to you.
I have some questions that come to
mind as well.
What's it about?
It's about the death of the Call.
The situation was stable.
Everything was going well, too.
Yeah, that's exactly what it was.
Since everything was going well...
... why did the Call die suddenly?
So why did he suddenly go into septic
shock?
I can't find the answers to these
questions.
Mr. Kenan, if you want, let's go to my
room and talk there.
Let's not talk like that, shall we?
- Glad. - Here you go.
Here you go, Master.
My teacher, believe me, I don't
understand what caused it.
Actually, I've been thinking about it for
two days.
How could it be?
So you have the same doubts, sir?
I mean, I'm the only one who doesn't
think so.
It exists because in the middle there is
a very unusual tablethat can be said.
With the rest of the call after the
operation
There is a big difference between the
values immediately before death.
One minute, one minute.
What are the differences, Professor?
Now, if there is another patient,
and if I were to say something
according to the values I have
As the cause of death, I call it organ
failure.
Organ failure?
How do you mean?
To the point where I am surprised, this is
exactly the Kenan Teacher.
Although all the findings
indicate organ failure
There is no reason for this.
ü,If you'll excuse me, can I look at
these reports?
Yes, of course, sir.
You were right, Professor.
It's really interesting.
Gokhan, never mind where I'm going.
Are the Tolga brothers here?
Hah, okay.
Now you take Tolga's brother and go
down to the garden.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Don't ask questions or do what I say,
come on.
Why is this trail so long?
Two different stitch marks.